{
  "levels": {
    "1": { "reward": 500 },
    "2": { "reward": 1000 },
    "3": { "reward": 2000 },
    "4": { "reward": 4000 },
    "5": { "reward": 8000 },
    "6": { "reward": 16000 },
    "7": { "reward": 32000 },
    "8": { "reward": 64000 },
    "9": { "reward": 125000 },
    "10": { "reward": 250000 },
    "11": { "reward": 500000 },
    "12": { "reward": 1000000 }
  },
  "questions": {
    "1": {
      "id": "11",
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Which of these chemical elements is not named after a scientist?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Einsteinium" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "Curium" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Fermium" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Gallium" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["D"]
    },
    "2": {
      "id": "22",
      "level": 2,
      "question": "What is the loudest animal on Earth?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Blue whale" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "African elephant" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Howler monkey" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Sperm whale" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["D"]
    },
    "3": {
      "id": "33",
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Which mathematician developed the first mechanical computer, the Difference Engine?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Alan Turing" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "Charles Babbage" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "John von Neumann" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Blaise Pascal" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["B"]
    },
    "4": {
      "id": "44",
      "level": 4,
      "question": "The concept of 'gravity' was first discovered by which famous physicist?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Albert Einstein" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "Isaac Newton" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Galileo Galilei" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Johannes Kepler" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["B"]
    },
    "5": {
      "id": "55",
      "level": 5,
      "question": "In Greek mythology, who is the goddess of wisdom?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Aphrodite" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "Hera" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Athena" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Artemis" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["C"]
    },
    "6": {
      "id": "66",
      "level": 6,
      "question": "Which composer became deaf near the end of his life?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "Johann Sebastian Bach" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Ludwig van Beethoven" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Franz Schubert" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["C"]
    },
    "7": {
      "id": "77",
      "level": 7,
      "question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Tungsten?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "T" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "W" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Tu" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Ts" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["B"]
    },
    "8": {
      "id": "88",
      "level": 8,
      "question": "Which of these countries does not have a president?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Germany" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "United Kingdom" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Italy" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Israel" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["B"]
    },
    "9": {
      "id": "99",
      "level": 9,
      "question": "What is the name of the first artificial Earth satellite, launched by the Soviet Union in 1957?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Sputnik" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "Vostok" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Laika" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Mir" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["A"]
    },
    "10": {
      "id": "1010",
      "level": 10,
      "question": "Which philosopher is attributed with the quote 'I can resist everything except temptation'?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Søren Kierkegaard" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "Friedrich Nietzsche" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Oscar Wilde" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Jean-Paul Sartre" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["C"]
    },
    "11": {
      "id": "1111",
      "level": 11,
      "question": "The Kármán Line, the boundary between Earth's atmosphere and outer space, is at what altitude above sea level?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "52 miles (84 kilometers)" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "62 miles (100 kilometers)" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "76 miles (122 kilometers)" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "100 miles (160 kilometers)" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["B"]
    },
    "12": {
      "id": "1212",
      "level": 12,
      "question": "In what field was the Nobel Prize first awarded posthumously?",
      "answers": [
        { "option": "A", "text": "Peace" },
        { "option": "B", "text": "Chemistry" },
        { "option": "C", "text": "Literature" },
        { "option": "D", "text": "Medicine" }
      ],
      "correctAnswers": ["D"]
    }
  }
}
